Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- Stars to be re-observed, 1875; phaedra1740 (Box 73)
  Date inferred
  KG11366.736
  U15
- Star places, 1875/1876; phaedra1741 (Box 73)
  KG11366.737
  U16
- K'K D D', 1870; phaedra1742 (Box 73)
  KG11366.738
  U17
- K'K D D', 1870; phaedra1743 (Box 73)
  KG11366.739
  U18
- Zero stars, Reduction to apparent place, 1875; phaedra1744 (Box 73)
  KG11366.740
  U19
- Table for reductions, 1875; phaedra1745 (Box 73)
  KG11366.741
  U20
- Fundamental Stars, Ephemerides, 1879; phaedra1746 (Box 73)
  KG11366.742
  U22
- Fundamental Stars, Ephemerides, 1879; phaedra1747 (Box 73)
  KG11366.743
  U23
- Working Lists, Fundamental Stars, 1879; phaedra1748 (Box 73)
  KG11366.744
  U24
- Working Lists, Fundamental Stars, 1879; phaedra1749 (Box 73)
  KG11366.745
  U25
- Longitude Campaign - Observations and Reductions, 1872/1873; phaedra1750 (Box 73)
  KG11366.746
  U27
- Miscellaneous Observations, 1881; phaedra1751 (Box 73)
  KG11366.747
  U28
  Contributor: Anna Winlock
  Includes correspondence to William Rogers from Anna Winlock
- Montreal Cambridge Longitude Observations, 1883; phaedra1752 (Box 73)
  KG11366.748
  U30
- Longitude Campaign: Montreal- Cambridge, 1883; phaedra1753 (Box 73)
  KG11366.749
  U31
- General Catalog List, 1872; phaedra1754 (Box 73)
  KG11366.750
  U34
- Observations, 1875; phaedra1755 (Box 73)
  KG11366.751
  U37
  Contents/title unknown
- Observations with Median Circle and Russian Transit, 1873; phaedra1756 (Box 73)
  KG11366.752
- Chronograph Record, 1870; phaedra1757 (Box 73)
  KG11366.753
  U40
  Henry Gannett
- List of Polar Stars with Dates of Observations, 1885; phaedra1758 (Box 73)
  KG11366.754
  U41
- Flexure Colimation Runs, 1880; phaedra1759 (Box 73)
  KG11366.755
- Investigation of Circle Observations, 1879; phaedra1760 (Box 73)
  KG11366.756
- Longitude of Circle Errors, 1881; phaedra1761 (Box 73)
  KG11366.757
- Investigation of Circle - Discussion, 1875; phaedra1762 (Box 73)
  KG11366.758
- Investigation of Errors of West Circle from Stops, 1884; phaedra1763 (Box 73)
  KG11366.759
- Investigation of Circle, 1877/1879; phaedra1764 (Box 73)
  KG11366.760
- Investigation of Circle Observations, 1871/1879; phaedra1765 (Box 73)
  KG11366.761
- Investigation of Errors of West Circle from Stops, 1884/1885; phaedra1766 (Box 73)
  KG11366.762
- Investigation of Errors of West Circle from Stops, 1885-04-15/1885-06-02; phaedra1767 (Box 74)
  KG11366.763
- Investigation of Errors of West Circle from Stops, 1885-06-04/1885-07-08; phaedra1768 (Box 74)
  KG11366.764
- Investigation of Errors of West Circle from Stops, 1885; phaedra1769 (Box 74)
  KG11366.765
- Investigation of Circle Observations, 1879; phaedra1770 (Box 74)
  KG11366.766
- Jupiter Eclipses and Variable Stars, 1900; phaedra1771 (Box 74)
  KG11366.767
- Jupiter Eclipses and Variable Stars, 1902; phaedra1772 (Box 74)
  KG11366.768
- Jupiter Eclipses and Variable Stars, 1894; phaedra1773 (Box 74)
  KG11366.769
- Jupiter Eclipses and Variable Stars, 1903; phaedra1774 (Box 74)
  KG11366.770
  L.H. Thibault, R.W. Lynn
- Variable Stars Zone P.M. XI, 1900; phaedra1775 (Box 74)
  KG11366.771
- Various Stars Zone P.M. XII, 1900; phaedra1776 (Box 74)
  KG11366.772
- Arequipa Time Book No.1, 1891/1892; phaedra1777 (Box 74)
  KG11366.773
- Chronograph comparisons, 1892-01-04/1892-12-12; phaedra1778 (Box 74)
  KG11366.774
- Comparison of Waltham Clock with South clock, 1878; phaedra1779 (Box 74)
  KG11366.775
- Error of Sidereal Clock, 1908; phaedra1780 (Box 74)
  KG11366.776
- Error of Sidereal Clock, 1913; phaedra1781 (Box 74)
  KG11366.777
  John A. Dunne, W.H.
- Error of Sidereal Clock, 1911; phaedra1782 (Box 74)
  KG11366.778
- Error of Sidereal Clock, 1910; phaedra1783 (Box 74)
  KG11366.779
- Observations, 1876; phaedra1784 (Box 74)
  KG11366.780
- Time book, 1875; phaedra1785 (Box 74)
  KG11366.781
- Time book, 1874; phaedra1786 (Box 74)
  KG11366.782
- Time book, 1874; phaedra1787 (Box 74)
  KG11366.783
- Time book, 1874; phaedra1788 (Box 74)
  KG11366.784
- Time Service (Clock Errors), 1879; phaedra1789 (Box 74)
  KG11366.785
- Clock Errors, 1878; phaedra1790 (Box 75)
  KG11366.786
- Time Service, 1888/1890; phaedra1791 (Box 75)
  KG11366.787
- Time Service, 1890/1891; phaedra1792 (Box 75)
  KG11366.788
- Time Service, 1891; phaedra1793 (Box 75)
  KG11366.789
- Time Service and Russian Transit, 1877; phaedra1794 (Box 75)
  KG11366.790
- Check Readings of Sheets of Observations for longitude, 1871; phaedra1795 (Box 75)
  KG11366.791
- Russian Transit, 1883; phaedra1796 (Box 75)
  KG11366.792
- Time Service, Clock Errors and Russian Transit, 1877; phaedra1797 (Box 75)
  KG11366.793
- Time Service, Clock Errors and Russian Transit, 1877; phaedra1798 (Box 75)
  KG11366.794
  Leonard Waldo, Joseph F. McCormack, William A. Rogers
- Time Service, Clock Comparison, 1881; phaedra1799 (Box 75)
  KG11366.795
  Frank Waldo, Winslow Upton, Leonard Waldo
- Level of East Transit, 1877; phaedra1800 (Box 75)
  KG11366.796
- Time Service, 1887/1888; phaedra1801 (Box 75)
  KG11366.797
- Time Service, 1882/1883; phaedra1802 (Box 75)
  KG11366.798
  Contributor: William A. Rogers
- Time Service, 1892/1894; phaedra1803 (Box 75)
  KG11366.799
- Time Service, 1880; phaedra1804 (Box 75)
  KG11366.800
  Harriet Wace
- Time Service Clock Comparisons, 1879/1880; phaedra1805 (Box 75)
  KG11366.801
  Frank Waldo, John R. Edmands
- Time Service Clock Comparisons, 1878/1879; phaedra1806 (Box 75)
  KG11366.802
  Leonard Waldo, Arthur Searle, Winslow Upton, Frank Waldo
- References book: Stars, Asteroids, etc. under observation, 1880; phaedra1807 (Box 75)
  Date unstated, inferred
  KG11366.803
- Errata in Rogers' AGC Catalogue, 1904; phaedra1808 (Box 75)
  KG11366.804
- Meridian Circle - General Record, 1879-05-05/1880-03-10; phaedra1809 (Box 76)
  KG11366.805
  1879phae.proj.1809R
- Constellations, 1871; phaedra1810 (Box 76)
  KG11366.806
  1871phae.proj.1810.
- Working List of Star Data, 1871; phaedra1811 (Box 76)
  KG11366.807
  1871phae.proj.1811.
- Working List of Star Data for 1880, 1880/1881; phaedra1812 (Box 76)
  KG11366.808
  1880phae.proj.1812.
- Constellation Data, 1879/1880; phaedra1813 (Box 76)
  KG11366.809
  1879phae.proj.1813.
- Reduction of Bonn Observations from 1855 to 1875, 1892; phaedra1814 (Box 76)
  KG11366.810
  1892phae.proj.1814.
- Discordant Stars, 1890; phaedra1815 (Box 76)
  KG11366.811
  1890phae.proj.1815.
- Reports on Observations of Stars in Northern Hemisphere up to 9th magnitude Pulkovo, 1879; phaedra1816 (Box 76)
  KG11366.812
  1879phae.proj.1816.
- Star Reduction, 1890; phaedra1817 (Box 76)
  KG11366.813
  1890phae.proj.1817.
- Measure of Plates, 1890; phaedra1818 (Box 76)
  KG11366.814
  1890phae.proj.1818.
- Computations - Longitude and Latitude of Bolivian and Peruvian Stations, no. 2, 1894; phaedra1819 (Box 76)
  KG11366.815
  1894phae.proj.1819.
  After title pages, notebook is blank
- Zone Observations, 1883/1884; phaedra1820 (Box 76)
  KG11366.816
  1883phae.proj.1820.
- Measurements, Micrometer, no. 1, 1894/1897; phaedra1821 (Box 76)
  KG11366.817
  1894phae.proj.1821R
- Sun Images, 1880; phaedra1822 (Box 76)
  KG11366.818
  1880phae.proj.1822.
  One page of notes only
- Miscellaneous Notes, 1900; phaedra1823 (Box 76)
  KG11366.819
  D.C. Bard
  1900phae.proj.1823B
- Chronograph Sheet readings, 1884-05-29/1884-12-03; phaedra1824 (Box 76)
  KG11366.820
  1884phae.proj.1824.
- Computation of Residuals, 1900; phaedra1825 (Box 76)
  Date not stated. Inferred from surrounding books
  KG11366.821
  1900phae.proj.1825.
- Correction for Error, 1869/1870; phaedra1826 (Box 76)
  KG11366.822
  1869phae.proj.1826.
- Observation of Southern Variable Stars, 1899/1904; phaedra1827 (Box 76)
  KG11366.823
  Harvard College Observatory, Benjamin F. Wyleth
  1899phae.proj.1827W
- Nautical Almanac, 1883; phaedra1828 (Box 76)
  KG11366.824
  1883phae.proj.1828.
- Lunar Brightness, 1881; phaedra1829 (Box 76)
  KG11366.825
  1881phae.proj.1829.
- 12-inch Horizontal Telescope Records, XII., 1899; phaedra1830 (Box 77)
  KG11366.826
  Arville Walker, Henrietta S. Leavitt
  1899phae.proj.1830W
- Satellite IV, 1888/1890; phaedra1831 (Box 77)
  KG11366.827
  1888phae.proj.1831.
- Reductions, 1888/1890; phaedra1832 (Box 77)
  KG11366.828
  1888phae.proj.1832.
- Bibliography, 1890; phaedra1833 (Box 77)
  KG11366.829
  1890phae.proj.1833.
- Observations and Reductions Part II, 1876; phaedra1834 (Box 77)
  KG11366.830
  Sidney Wetmore
  1876phae.proj.1834W
- Observations and Reductions Part III, 1876/1880; phaedra1835 (Box 77)
  KG11366.831
  1876phae.proj.1835W
- Re-readings of Chronograph Sheets, 1880; phaedra1836 (Box 77)
  KG11366.832
  1880phae.proj.1836.
- Investigations of Division Errors of Circle East, 1880/1881; phaedra1837 (Box 77)
  KG11366.833
  1880phae.proj.1837R
- Chronograph Readings, 1881; phaedra1838 (Box 77)
  KG11366.834
  Harriet Stevens, Arville Walker, Leonard Waldo
  1881phae.proj.1838S
- Readings of Chronograph Sheets, 1879-02-15/1879-12-31; phaedra1839 (Box 77)
  KG11366.835
  1879phae.proj.1839W
- Star Data, 1884/1885; phaedra1840 (Box 77)
  KG11366.836
  1884phae.proj.1840.
- Star Data, 1882; phaedra1841 (Box 77)
  KG11366.837
  1882phae.proj.1841.
- Star and Comet Data, 1881/1884; phaedra1842 (Box 77)
  KG11366.838
  Palmer C. Ricketts
  1881phae.proj.1842R
- Reductions, 1880/1881; phaedra1843 (Box 77)
  KG11366.839
  1880phae.proj.1843C
- Comet Data and Comparison Stars, 1881; phaedra1844 (Box 77)
  KG11366.840
  1881phae.proj.1844.
  Observations by "P"
- Time Service, 1885/1886; phaedra1845 (Box 77)
  KG11366.841
  1885phae.proj.1845R
- Dates of Observations of Zone Stars for 1883 and 1884, 1883/1884; phaedra1846 (Box 77)
  KG11366.842
  1883phae.proj.1846.
- Miscellaneous Star Observations, 1890; phaedra1847 (Box 77)
  Date inferred from surrounding materials
  KG11366.843
  1890phae.proj.1847.
- Star Observations, 1890; phaedra1848 (Box 77)
  KG11366.844
  1890phae.proj.1848.
- Zone Observations, 1884; phaedra1849 (Box 77)
  KG11366.845
  1884phae.proj.1849.
- Fundamental Zone Star Circle Readings, 1885; phaedra1850 (Box 77)
  KG11366.846
  1885phae.proj.1850.
- Current Observations of Variable Stars, 1895/1896; phaedra1851 (Box 78)
  KG11366.847
  1895phae.proj.1851.
- Record of Observations, 1898/1899; phaedra1852 (Box 78)
  KG11366.848
  F.W. Grover
  1898phae.proj.1852G
- Variable Star Observations, 1899/1900; phaedra1853 (Box 78)
  KG11366.849
  H.C. Bailey
  1899phae.proj.1853B
- Absolute Work Runs 1879, 80, 81, 1879/1899; phaedra1854 (Box 78)
  KG11366.850
  1879phae.proj.1854.
- [Variable Stars], 1883/1884; phaedra1855 (Box 78)
  KG11366.851
  1883phae.proj.1855.
- West Dome 6.25-inch, 1883; phaedra1856 (Box 78)
  KG11366.852
  1883phae.proj.1856C
- West Dome 6.25-inch, 1883; phaedra1857 (Box 78)
  KG11366.853
  1883phae.proj.1857C
- West Dome 6.25-inch, 1896/1898; phaedra1858 (Box 78)
  KG11366.854
  1896phae.proj.1858D
- Wedge Zones, 1887; phaedra1859 (Box 78)
  KG11366.855
  1887phae.proj.1859.
- Correction to Ephemerides - Jupiter's Satellites, 1920; phaedra1860 (Box 78)
  Date inferred from notebook type
  KG11366.856
  1920phae.proj.1860.
  Three pages of content (charts)
- Final Adopted Magnitudes: Comp Stars for Variables, 1901; phaedra1861 (Box 78)
  KG11366.857
  1901phae.proj.1861.
- Final Adopted Magnitudes: Comp Stars for Variables, 1900; phaedra1862 (Box 78)
  KG11366.858
  1900phae.proj.1862.
- Variable and Other Stars, 1889/1890; phaedra1863 (Box 78)
  KG11366.859
  1889phae.proj.1863.
- Variable Star Observations, 1894/1895; phaedra1864 (Box 78)
  KG11366.860
  1894phae.proj.1864B
- Variable Stars, 1898/1899; phaedra1865 (Box 78)
  KG11366.861
  1898phae.proj.1865.
- Computation Book, 1899/1900; phaedra1866 (Box 78)
  KG11366.862
  1899phae.proj.1866.
- Computation Book, 1902; phaedra1867 (Box 78)
  KG11366.863
  1902phae.proj.1867.
- Wedge Photometer Zone Stars, 1894; phaedra1868 (Box 78)
  KG11366.864
  1894phae.proj.1868.
- Meridian Photometry, 1881/1884; phaedra1869 (Box 78)
  KG11366.865
  1881phae.proj.1869.
- Multiplet Theory (H.N. Russell) - Notes, 1925; phaedra1870 (Box 78)
  KG11366.866
  1925phae.proj.1870.
- Plates to be Examined re. Peters' Zones, 1877/1878; phaedra1871 (Box 79)
  KG11366.867
  1877phae.proj.1871.
- Equatorial Zones, 1877; phaedra1872 (Box 79)
  KG11366.868
  R21
  1877phae.proj.1872.
- Location of Comparison Stars for Variables, 1894; phaedra1873 (Box 79)
  KG11366.869
  1894phae.proj.1873.
- Crown Flint Optical Data, 1902/1903; phaedra1874 (Box 79)
  KG11366.870
  1902phae.proj.1874.
- Chronograph Record, 1870-06-22/1870-11-01; phaedra1875 (Box 79)
  KG11366.871
  1870phae.proj.1875.
- Chronograph Record, 1870-07-12/1871-06-12; phaedra1876 (Box 79)
  KG11366.872
  1870phae.proj.1876.
- Psychrometer comparisons at Arequipa and other Stations, 1896/1897; phaedra1877 (Box 79)
  KG11366.873
  Robert DeCourcy Ward
  1896phae.proj.1877D
- Miscellaneous Notes and Work Plans, 1862/1869; phaedra1878 (Box 79)
  KG11366.874
  1862phae.proj.1878.
- Variable Star Observations, 1901; phaedra1879 (Box 79)
  KG11366.875
  1901phae.proj.1879C
  See also KG11365.778
- Thermometer Readings, 1890; phaedra1880 (Box 79)
  Date inferred from surroundings. No year given.
  KG11366.876
  1890phae.proj.1880.
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 862, 872, 873, 1911-01-11/1911-01-16; phaedra1881 (Box 79)
  KG11366.877
  Mary Fowler
  1911phae.proj.1881F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 864, 865, 878, 879, 1911-01-15/1911-01-17; phaedra1882 (Box 79)
  KG11366.878
  1911phae.proj.1882F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 920, 921, 922, 932, 1911-02-15/1911-02-18; phaedra1883 (Box 79)
  KG11366.879
  1911phae.proj.1883F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 933, 934, 966, 967, 1911-02-18/1911-03-09; phaedra1884 (Box 79)
  KG11366.880
  1911phae.proj.1884F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 968, 972, 974, 977, 1911-03-09/1911-03-13; phaedra1885 (Box 79)
  KG11366.881
  1911phae.proj.1885F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 978, 979, 1028, 1029, 1911-03-13/1911-04-10; phaedra1886 (Box 79)
  KG11366.882
  1911phae.proj.1886F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1030, 1034, 1035, 1049, 1911-04-10/1911-04-16; phaedra1887 (Box 79)
  KG11366.883
  1911phae.proj.1887F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1050, 1051, 1067, 1068, 1069, 1911-04-16/1911-05-03; phaedra1888 (Box 79)
  KG11366.884
  1911phae.proj.1888F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1041, 1042, 1043, 1078, 1079, 1911-04-12/1911-05-04; phaedra1889 (Box 79)
  KG11366.885
  1911phae.proj.1889F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1080, 1085, 1086, 1122, 1092, 1911-05-04/1911-06-03; phaedra1890 (Box 79)
  KG11366.886
  1911phae.proj.1890F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1093, 1094, 1123, 1124, 1125, 1911-05-06/1911-06-07; phaedra1891 (Box 79)
  KG11366.887
  1911phae.proj.1891F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1126, 1128, 1911-06-07/1911-06-08; phaedra1892 (Box 79)
  KG11366.888
  1911phae.proj.1892F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1129, 1130, 1911-06-08; phaedra1893 (Box 79)
  KG11366.889
  1911phae.proj.1893F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1301, 1302, 1303, 1911-10-07; phaedra1894 (Box 79)
  KG11366.890
  Vol. 15 [sic]
  1911phae.proj.1894F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1166, 1257, 1911-07-07/1911-09-10; phaedra1895 (Box 79)
  KG11366.891
  1911phae.proj.1895F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1304, 1305, 1911-10-07; phaedra1896 (Box 79)
  KG11366.892
  1911phae.proj.1896F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1307, 1308, 1309, 1911-10-07; phaedra1897 (Box 79)
  KG11366.893
  Vol. 17
  1911phae.proj.1897F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1310, 1311, 1312, 1911-10-07; phaedra1898 (Box 79)
  KG11366.894
  1911phae.proj.1898F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1313, 1314, 1315, 1911-10-07; phaedra1899 (Box 79)
  KG11366.895
  1911phae.proj.1899F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1318, 1319, 1331, 1911-10-09/1911-10-13; phaedra1900 (Box 79)
  KG11366.896
  1911phae.proj.1900F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1168, 1911-07-07; phaedra1901 (Box 79)
  KG11366.897
  1911phae.proj.1901F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1332, 1375, 1376, 1911-10-13/1911-11-02; phaedra1902 (Box 79)
  KG11366.898
  1911phae.proj.1902F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1380, 1381, 1397, 1911-11-03/1911-11-05; phaedra1903 (Box 80)
  KG11366.899
  1911phae.proj.1903F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1398, 1402, 1403, 1911-11-05/1911-11-07; phaedra1904 (Box 80)
  KG11366.900
  1911phae.proj.1904F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1407, 1408, 1412, 1911-11-12/1911-11-13; phaedra1905 (Box 80)
  KG11366.901
  1911phae.proj.1905F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1413, 1446, 1445, 1911-11-13/1911-11-29; phaedra1906 (Box 80)
  KG11366.902
  Vol. 26
  1911phae.proj.1906F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1452, 1453, 1462, 1911-12-02/1911-12-04; phaedra1907 (Box 80)
  KG11366.903
  Vol. 27
  1911phae.proj.1907F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1463, 1518, 1519, 1911-12-04/1911-12-30; phaedra1908 (Box 80)
  KG11366.904
  Vol. 28
  1911phae.proj.1908F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1520, 1521, 1524, 1912-01-01/1912-01-03; phaedra1909 (Box 80)
  KG11366.905
  Vol. 29
  1912phae.proj.1909F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1525, 1542, 1543, 1912-01-03/1912-01-09; phaedra1910 (Box 80)
  KG11366.906
  Vol. 30
  1912phae.proj.1910F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1549, 1550, 1590, 1912-01-10/1912-01-27; phaedra1911 (Box 80)
  KG11366.907
  Vol. 31
  1912phae.proj.1911F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1591, 1598, 1912-01-27/1912-01-31; phaedra1912 (Box 80)
  KG11366.908
  Vol. 32
  1912phae.proj.1912F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1599, 1606, 1912-01-31/1912-02-06; phaedra1913 (Box 80)
  KG11366.909
  Vol. 33
  1912phae.proj.1913F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1607, 1662, 1668, 1912-02-06/1912-02-27; phaedra1914 (Box 80)
  KG11366.910
  Vol. 34
  1912phae.proj.1914F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1669, 1674, 1675, 1912-02-27/1912-02-28; phaedra1915 (Box 80)
  KG11366.911
  Vol. 35
  1912phae.proj.1915F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1682, 1683, 1696, 1912-02-29/1912-03-02; phaedra1916 (Box 80)
  KG11366.912
  Vol. 36
  1912phae.proj.1916F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1697, 1702, 1703, 1912-03-02/1912-03-05; phaedra1917 (Box 80)
  KG11366.913
  Vol. 37
  1912phae.proj.1917F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1737, 1739, 1743, 1912-03-25/1912-03-27; phaedra1918 (Box 80)
  KG11366.914
  Vol. 38
  1912phae.proj.1918F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1744, 1747, 1912-03-27/1912-03-29; phaedra1919 (Box 80)
  KG11366.915
  Vol. 39
  1912phae.proj.1919F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1749, 1750, 1751, 1912-03-29/1912-03-30; phaedra1920 (Box 80)
  KG11366.916
  Vol. 40
  1912phae.proj.1920F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1759, 1760, 1790, 1912-04-03/1912-04-25; phaedra1921 (Box 80)
  KG11366.917
  Vol. 41
  1912phae.proj.1921F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1791, 1795, 1912-04-25/1912-04-27; phaedra1922 (Box 80)
  KG11366.918
  Vol. 42
  1912phae.proj.1922F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1796, 1801, 1802, 1912-04-27/1912-04-30; phaedra1923 (Box 80)
  KG11366.919
  Vol. 43
  1912phae.proj.1923F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1808, 1809, 1826, 1912-05-02/1912-05-25; phaedra1924 (Box 80)
  KG11366.920
  Vol. 44
  1912phae.proj.1924F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1827, 1884, 1912-05-27/1912-07-02; phaedra1925 (Box 80)
  KG11366.921
  Vol. 45
  1912phae.proj.1925F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1885, 1889, 1890, 1912-07-02/1912-07-03; phaedra1926 (Box 80)
  KG11366.922
  Vol. 46
  1912phae.proj.1926F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1930, 1931, 1956, 1912-08-05/1912-08-27; phaedra1927 (Box 80)
  KG11366.923
  Vol. 47
  1912phae.proj.1927F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1957, 1963, 1964, 1912-08-27/1912-08-29; phaedra1928 (Box 80)
  KG11366.924
  Vol. 48
  1912phae.proj.1928F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1973, 1974, 1912-08-30; phaedra1929 (Box 80)
  KG11366.925
  Vol. 49
  1912phae.proj.1929F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1980. 1981, 2009, 1912-08-31/1912-09-25; phaedra1930 (Box 80)
  KG11366.926
  Vol. 50
  1912phae.proj.1930F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2010, 2011, 2012, 1912-09-25/1912-09-27; phaedra1931 (Box 80)
  KG11366.927
  Vol. 51
  1912phae.proj.1931F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2014, 2015, 2074, 1912-09-29/1912-10-21; phaedra1932 (Box 80)
  KG11366.928
  Vol. 52
  1912phae.proj.1932F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2076, 2081, 2082, 1912-10-21/1912-10-30; phaedra1933 (Box 80)
  KG11366.929
  Vol. 53
  1912phae.proj.1933F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2093, 2094, 2145, 1912-11-02/1912-11-18; phaedra1934 (Box 80)
  KG11366.930
  Vol. 54
  1912phae.proj.1934F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2146, 2172, 1912-11-18/1912-11-20; phaedra1935 (Box 80)
  KG11366.931
  Vol. 55
  1912phae.proj.1935F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2173, 2180, 2181, 1912-11-20/1912-11-21; phaedra1936 (Box 80)
  KG11366.932
  Vol. 56
  1912phae.proj.1936F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2184, 2185, 2234, 1912-11-25/1912-11-30; phaedra1937 (Box 80)
  KG11366.933
  Vol. 57
  1912phae.proj.1937F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2235, 2367, 2368, 1912-11-30/1912-12-19; phaedra1938 (Box 80)
  KG11366.934
  Vol. 58
  1912phae.proj.1938F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2374, 2375, 2377, 1912-12-20/1912-12-24; phaedra1939 (Box 80)
  KG11366.935
  Vol. 59
  1912phae.proj.1939F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2378, 2386, 2387, 1912-12-24/1912-12-25; phaedra1940 (Box 80)
  KG11366.936
  Vol. 60
  1912phae.proj.1940F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2493, 2494, 2782, 1913-01-22/1913-02-15; phaedra1941 (Box 80)
  KG11366.937
  Vol. 61
  1913phae.proj.1941F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2783, 2797, 2798, 1913-02-15/1913-02-18; phaedra1942 (Box 80)
  KG11366.938
  Vol. 62
  1913phae.proj.1942F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2371, 2182, 2368, 1912-11-21/1912-12-19; phaedra1943 (Box 80)
  KG11366.939
  Vol. 63
  1912phae.proj.1943F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2992, 2994, 3008, 1913-03-17/1913-03-18; phaedra1944 (Box 81)
  KG11366.940
  Vol. 64
  1913phae.proj.1944F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3010, 3023, 3024, 1913-03-18/1913-03-19; phaedra1945 (Box 81)
  KG11366.941
  Vol. 65
  1913phae.proj.1945F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 1698, 1748, 1912-03-02/1912-03-29; phaedra1946 (Box 81)
  KG11366.942
  1912phae.proj.1946F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 2751, 2752, 1913-02-14/1913-02-14; phaedra1947 (Box 81)
  KG11366.943
  Vol. 66
  1913phae.proj.1947F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3045, 3046, 3189, 1913-03-22/1913-04-17; phaedra1948 (Box 81)
  KG11366.944
  Vol. 67
  1913phae.proj.1948F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3215, 3376, 1913-04-19/1913-05-12; phaedra1949 (Box 81)
  KG11366.945
  Vol. 68
  1913phae.proj.1949F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3377, 3385, 3384, 1913-05-12/1913-05-14; phaedra1950 (Box 81)
  KG11366.946
  Vol. 69
  1913phae.proj.1950F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3485, 3486, 3535, 1913-06-13/1913-07-22; phaedra1951 (Box 81)
  KG11366.947
  Vol. 70
  1913phae.proj.1951F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3536, 3601, 1913-07-22/1913-08-12; phaedra1952 (Box 81)
  KG11366.948
  Vol. 71
  1913phae.proj.1952F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3648, 3649, 1913-08-19/1913-08-19; phaedra1953 (Box 81)
  KG11366.949
  Vol. 72
  1913phae.proj.1953F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3669, 3783, 1913-08-20/1913-09-10; phaedra1954 (Box 81)
  KG11366.950
  Vol. 73
  1913phae.proj.1954F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3784, 3811, 1913-09-10/1913-09-13; phaedra1955 (Box 81)
  KG11366.951
  Vol. 74
  1913phae.proj.1955F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3812 3844, 1913-09-13/1913-09-14; phaedra1956 (Box 81)
  KG11366.952
  Vol. 75
  1913phae.proj.1956F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3846, 3856, 1913-09-14/1913-09-15; phaedra1957 (Box 81)
  KG11366.953
  Vol. 76
  1913phae.proj.1957F
- Harvard Lunar Plates, Plates 3857, 4096, 1913-09-15/1913-10-21; phaedra1958 (Box 81)
  KG11366.954
  Vol. 77
  1913phae.proj.1958F